TRISHA SINGH RAJPUT

ASSISTANT DIGITAL STRATEGY MANAGER

singhruchi720@gmail.com | 9770234047 | www.linkedin.com/in/trisha-singh-rajput | Gurgaon

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a versatile & goal-oriented professional with 4.8 years of experience in Sales & Marketing, Content Optimization, Social Media Operations and Campaign Management across three industries, i.e. Marketing and PR, ecommerce and education. With successfully running a YouTube Channel; I have expertise in Branding, Promotions, Team Management, Digital Marketing & Competitor Analysis and have driven revenue gains and brand awareness through intelligent use of Digital Marketing landscape.

SKILLS

CORE SKILLS: Content Marketing, Brand Strategy Operations, Digital Marketing, Social media marketing, Market Research, SEM, Campaign Management, Media Planning, Cross-Functional Coordination, Team Management **SOFTWARE AND TOOLS:** Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Creator Studio, Google Trends

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT DIGITAL STRATEGY MANAGER

GURGAON

Bulbul - Video Shopping App

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

- Successfully managing the overall operations relating to brand equity health scores; mapping the performance of all social media platforms of Bulbul by spreading awareness & leading multiple brand campaigns
- Planning & executing all the Digital Marketing strategies including Content Marketing, SEO of the PWA and Youtube Channel, Social Media Advertising Campaigns for branding and Social Shopping to the e-commerce site & app
- Coordinating with the digital agencies to help optimise the media campaigns. Also, ensuring & tracking the performance of all marketing campaigns and measuring the same with the ROI & KPIs
- Successfully increased traffic on social media accounts by 50% with the help of multiple campaigns
- Initiated two Branding campaigns named 'Video Dekha Kya' & 'Watch from Home' and handling them from ideation to its implementation

SHADOW INTERN TO CEO

MUMBAI

Iprospects - Digital marketing agency

June 2019 - August 2019

- Worked on Content and paid media projects related to brand awareness of Shaze and Lido Learning, and brand performance of Raymond- Colour Plus and Bobbinmart.
- Did market research based on the target segment, competitor analysis, keyword analysis, Google Adwords, target base, social media targeting, GDN targeting and media planning.

PROJECT & STRATEGY MANAGER

RAIPUR

Mahendras Education Pvt Ltd.

June 2017 - July 2018

- Successfully conducted smart classes for General Studies subjects, related to: Bank, SSC, PSC
- Managed the marketing strategy for Chhattisgarh region

MARKETING AND TEAM MANAGER

BHILAI

Blue8 media

June 2014 - Jun 2017

- Successfully developed the marketing plans and on-ground promotions for clients and Conducted over 20+ brand promotional events and did surveys under pre-launch marketing campaigns
- Worked with multiple clients and managed key accounts like: BIMS, Vidyalankar, Renault KWID, TATA Motors-Zest, Madame, Chemistry, Quest & others

EDUCATION HISTORY

- MBA from Vedica Scholars Programme for Women, Batch of 2019, Delhi | Secured 80.4%
- DIGITAL MARKETING Course from Kraftshala Integrated Digital Marketing Program, 2019 | Secured Industry Creds score of 73
- B.TECH. HONS. (Electronics & Instrumentation) from Shri Shankaracharya College of Engineering and Technology, Bhilai | Secured 8.52 CPI